Contact Management System
Problem Statement:
Create a simple contact management system that allows users to manage a list of contacts.
Features:
	1	Add a Contact: Add a new contact with name, phone number, and email.
	2	View All Contacts: Display all contacts.
	3	Search for a Contact: Find a contact by name.
	4	Update Contact Information: Update the details of an existing contact.
	5	Delete a Contact: Remove a contact from the list.

Explanation:
	•	ContactManager Class: Manages the list of contacts using a list.
	•	Methods:
	◦	add_contact(): Adds a new contact.
	◦	view_contacts(): Displays all contacts.
	◦	search_contact(): Searches for a contact by name.
	◦	update_contact(): Updates the details of an existing contact.
	◦	delete_contact(): Deletes a contact from the list.
	•	Main Function: Provides a menu-driven interface to interact with the contact manager.
